Guide to the American School Kikungshan and American School Kikungshan Association Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Collected Material, 1921-2003; Series V
  - Miscellaneous
    - 2 Scrolls. One is a calligraphy done by Rev. Yin Yang for the 2003 ASk reunion. The other is a sign from the 1994 reunion., 1994, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 97)
    - Misc. slides: ASK Reunion, 1980; Slides from Kittlesby Plaque Dedication, 1981; China, May-June 1982; Presentation by Katherine Edwins Schumm at 1988 ASK Reunion, "Remembering ASK Parents Missionaries to Chinese in Honan" (Box 12, Folder 98)